# **Gabriel Akinshola**

35, Engr. Odesola street, Alagbado, Lagos State • +234 8135843770 • gabrielakinshola3@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/gabriel-akinshola • x.com/gabbyextra • https://code021-raelle.github.io/myPortfolio

## **Software Engineer**

With 2+ years of experience, I have led a team to achieve a 20% increase in productivity in 6 months and developed an inventory management system that reduced excess stock levels by 25% in my current role as a procurement officer.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Upwork · 09/2023 - Present

Freelance

#### Freelancer • Full-time

 Acquired 4 new clients through direct outreach, increasing revenue by 25% and expanding the client base.

### Fiverr · 04/2023 - Present

Freelance

#### Team Leader · Full-time

- Led team to achieve 20% increase in productivity by implementing new workflow processes, resulting in improved efficiency and cost savings.
- Created a responsive website for an individual who's in need of a site for his business.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Computer Software Engineering**

Holberton School • 07/2023 - 08/2024

This is the ALX Software Engineering 12-months programme (https://www.alxafrica.com/software-engineering/). It's a project-oriented training mostly focused on web development but also on the basics of software engineering, namely: algorithms, data structures, programming paradigms, etc.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Responsive Web Design • 03/2024 - Present

freeCodeCamp

#### **SKILLS**

Bash, Bootstrap, C, CSS, DevOps, FLASK, Git, HTML, JavaScript, Python, React, Transcript, TypeScript, UI/UX